I've walked through all these halls before
这里走廊我全走过
I've been in and out of every door,
教室进出新知也无多,
There's nothin' in this school that I don't know
学校的信息尽在我掌握
In every class, my grade's the best
课程成绩这一切
The highest score on every test
对我都简单无差别
I think that means it's time for me to go
我想这代表是时候远走
I know there's more that's out there
未知存在这世界
And I just haven't found it yet
只是我不曾去了解
I know there's more that's out there
未知存在这世界
Another me I haven't met
新的自我等待迎接
Everyone here likes who I am
学生乐于和我见面
And it's not from a magic spell's command,
而这绝非我的魔咒所变,
My friends look past the things I've done before
朋友都原谅了我的过错
But still I miss those quests
但我想念那些
The mythic creatures, magic tests
神话生物魔法的一切
High school's great, sure, but who am I anymore?
高中虽好但我可还是我?
It's not that I'm ungrateful or trying to succeed
并非我不知感恩或贪图名利
But there's something left still missing,
但外面未知迷离,
something that I need
我想去寻觅
I know there's more that's out there
未知存在这世界
Maybe folks that need my help
帮忙也许有人要
I know there's more that's out there
未知存在这世界
Because I've seen it for myself
我见过所以我知晓
There's only so much this town can offer
这小镇有的只有这么多
And I'm not saying that's so bad
我的意思并非不屑
But I know there's more that's out there
但未知遍布这世界
'Cause it's a life that I once had
因我曾拥有那一切
Beyond these rooms, beyond these walls
房间之后 墙壁外廊
So much to learn, I can't see it all
还有很多未曾见识过
This town is home, this school is safe
小镇如家 设施完备
But how can I be home and still feel out of place?
但不是真的家怎么步入正轨?
And I know there's more that's out there
未知遍布在这世界
Another world to explore
比如另一个王国
And I know there's more that's out there
未知遍布在这世界
Am I wrong for wanting more?
想更多是否有错?
And I can't wait for it to happen
我迫不及待让它发生
But what it is I cannot say
但说不出它的是非
I just know there's more that's out there
只知道它在这世界
And it's calling out my name
呼唤我名字去追
And I'm searching for the answer
为答案我不惜波折
'Cause I feel I've lost my way
因我已经迷失方位
I may not know what's really out there
我也许不知其中详略
But I'll find out someday!
但答案终在结尾!
I'll find out someday...
就在那结尾...